https://www.wtvq.com/legal/

your password
Forgot your password?
Password recovery
Recover your password
your email
Search
[ditty_news_ticker id="349423"]
your email
A password will be e-mailed to you.
LATEST NEWS
EKU to give $1,000 bonuses as part of investing in staff; new provost named
Local News
Steve Rogers -
December 10, 2020 0
Ziegler named to replace Pogatshnik; Regents set goal of in-person graduation in May.
December 10, 2020 0
John Trimble is charged with murder in connection to the shooting death of another man, according to investigators.
Read more
UPDATE: Citing Washington, surveys, Beshear responds to GOP ‘priority’
Read more
Menorah lighting encourages acts of ‘goodness and kindness’
Local News
WTVQ News Desk -
December 10, 2020 0
On Thursday Chabad of The Bluegrass lit a public 10 foot Chanukkah menorah at the Lexington Government Center.
Read more
Mandates lifted on Monday, record cases but positivity rate drops 7th day
Local News
Steve Rogers -
December 10, 2020 0
Part of records cases may be from Thanksgiving.
Read more
Teachers offer input, thoughts on returning to in-person instruction
Local News
Steve Rogers -
December 10, 2020 0
Beshear, Glass to meet Friday to discuss input, options.
Read more
FDA approves Pfizer vaccine, could start next week in Kentucky
December 10, 2020 0
38 graduates from across the state.
December 10, 2020 0
A storm system will be approaching Friday. Winds will pick up out of the south, gusting up to 20 mph, with highs in the...
December 6, 2020 0
You and Santa struggling when it comes to finding the perfect gift for your little scientist? If so, Jason Lindsey, aka "Mr. Science," with...
December 3, 2020 0
Every now and then, you see a sunrise that really takes your breath away. This was the case Thursday morning at the Kentucky Horse...
November 19, 2020 0
A Red Flag Warning is in effect today from the mid-Mississippi Valley to the Ohio Valley. This includes parts of central and western Kentucky.
What's...
November 3, 2020 0
Hurricane Eta maintained category 4 status with winds of 145 mph Tuesday, bringing heavy rainfall and flooding to areas of Central America.
Read more
Hurricane Delta becomes the strongest storm named after a letter in the Greek alphabet
ABC 36 Storm Team
Alyssa Andrews -
October 6, 2020 0
Hurricane Delta became a category 4 hurricane Tuesday morning. This now classifies Delta as the strongest storm to ever be named after a letter...
Read more
Over 5 inches of rain fell over the weekend in some Kentucky counties
ABC 36 Storm Team
Alyssa Andrews -
September 14, 2020 0
Heavy showers and thunderstorms caused flash flooding issues across central Kentucky over the weekend. Rainfall totals from the Kentucky Mesonet at WKU show some...
Read more
Sports
SPORTS SECTIONSSports
36 Blitz
Solid Blue
High School Highlight Reel
LATEST SPORTS
SEC and ESPN/ABC reach milestone 10-year media agreement
athletics
Bryan Kennedy -
December 10, 2020 0
BIRMINGHAM, Alabama (December 10, 2020) - The Southeastern Conference and ESPN have finalized a milestone 10-year agreement that grants ABC and ESPN exclusive broadcast...
Read more
Student-Athlete of the Week: Avrey Rigney
athletics
Alyssa Andrews -
December 10, 2020 0
We head to Madison County to honor a freshman that’s already making a stamp on her varsity volleyball team.
Our student-athlete of the week is...
Read more
KHSAA votes to push back Boy’s/Girl’s Sweet 16, keep season start date
athletics
Bryan Kennedy -
December 10, 2020 0
LEXINGTON, KY (WTVQ) - The KHSAA Board of Control met on Thursday and another big decision was made regarding winter sports. The Board voted...
Read more
#1 Georgetown beats IU-Southeast, 82-72
athletics
Bryan Kennedy -
December 10, 2020 0
GEORGETOWN, Ky (GC Athletics) - Kyran Jones and Derrin Boyd helped to do the heavy lifting against a sharp-shooting IU Southeast team Wednesday. The...
Read more
Blair Green scores career high as No. 9 Kentucky rolls past Marshall
athletics
Bryan Kennedy -
December 9, 2020 0
LEXINGTON, Ky. (UK Athletics) – Junior Blair Green scored a career-high 17 points as the ninth-ranked Kentucky women's basketball team beat Marshall 79-45 on...
Read more
Lexington Legends no longer an affiliate of the Kansas City Royals
athletics
Bryan Kennedy -
December 9, 2020 0
LEXINGTON, KY (WTVQ) - The Lexington Legends are no longer the Single “A” Affiliate of the Kansas City Royals.
https://twitter.com/lexingtonlegend/status/1336718817523806214?s=21
The Royals moved their “A”...
Read more
Keeneland has 1,588 horses in January sale
Equestrian
Tom Kenny -
December 8, 2020 0
Keeneland will continue to offer online and phone bidding to enable buyers to participate in the January Sale remotely.
Read more
Keeneland catalogs 79 lots for December Digital Sale
Equestrian
Tom Kenny -
December 8, 2020 0
The sale will be held Tuesday, Dec. 15 as part of Keeneland’s Digital Sales Ring platform.
Read more
Contests
Lee & Hayley 12 Days of Giveaways
Student Athlete of the Week
Teacher of the Week
Cash for Holiday Gifts Giveaway
Golden Care Provider of Month
Community
LATEST NEWS
EKU to give $1,000 bonuses as part of investing in staff; new provost named
Local News
Steve Rogers -
December 10, 2020 0
Ziegler named to replace Pogatshnik; Regents set goal of in-person graduation in May.
Read more
Arrest made in fatal Johnson County shooting
Local News
Veronica Jean Seltzer -
December 10, 2020 0
John Trimble is charged with murder in connection to the shooting death of another man, according to investigators.
Read more
UPDATE: Citing Washington, surveys, Beshear responds to GOP ‘priority’
Local News
Erica Bivens -
December 10, 2020 0
Next year's legislative session convenes in January
Read more
Menorah lighting encourages acts of ‘goodness and kindness’
Local News
WTVQ News Desk -
December 10, 2020 0
On Thursday Chabad of The Bluegrass lit a public 10 foot Chanukkah menorah at the Lexington Government Center.
Read more
Mandates lifted on Monday, record cases but positivity rate drops 7th day
Local News
Steve Rogers -
December 10, 2020 0
Part of records cases may be from Thanksgiving.
Read more
Teachers offer input, thoughts on returning to in-person instruction
Local News
Steve Rogers -
December 10, 2020 0
Beshear, Glass to meet Friday to discuss input, options.
Read more
FDA approves Pfizer vaccine, could start next week in Kentucky
Local News
Steve Rogers -
December 10, 2020 0
First doses expected to be in Kentucky next week
Read more
Area officers among new police graduates, award winners
Local News
Steve Rogers -
December 10, 2020 0
38 graduates from across the state.
Read more
Weather
WEATHER SECTIONSWeather Forecast
Weather Maps
Forcht Bank Skyview
SnoWatch
Local Weather Headlines
WEATHER HEADLINES
Rain to start the weekend
ABC 36 Storm Team
Alyssa Andrews -
December 10, 2020 0
A storm system will be approaching Friday. Winds will pick up out of the south, gusting up to 20 mph, with highs in the...
Read more
Top Local STEM Toys for Christmas 2020
Local News
Jason Lindsey -
December 6, 2020 0
You and Santa struggling when it comes to finding the perfect gift for your little scientist? If so, Jason Lindsey, aka "Mr. Science," with...
Read more
Incredible sunrise from the Kentucky Horse Park
ABC 36 Storm Team
Alyssa Andrews -
December 3, 2020 0
Every now and then, you see a sunrise that really takes your breath away. This was the case Thursday morning at the Kentucky Horse...
Read more
Heading Out? Web sites offer road condition updates
Local News
Steve Rogers -
December 1, 2020 0
Salt stocked; plows prepped; crews on call
Read more
Red Flag Warning Thursday
ABC 36 Storm Team
Alyssa Andrews -
November 19, 2020 0
A Red Flag Warning is in effect today from the mid-Mississippi Valley to the Ohio Valley. This includes parts of central and western Kentucky.
What's...
Read more
Hurricane Eta Tuesday Update
ABC 36 Storm Team
Alyssa Andrews -
November 3, 2020 0
Hurricane Eta maintained category 4 status with winds of 145 mph Tuesday, bringing heavy rainfall and flooding to areas of Central America.
Read more
Hurricane Delta becomes the strongest storm named after a letter in the Greek alphabet
ABC 36 Storm Team
Alyssa Andrews -
October 6, 2020 0
Hurricane Delta became a category 4 hurricane Tuesday morning. This now classifies Delta as the strongest storm to ever be named after a letter...
Read more
Over 5 inches of rain fell over the weekend in some Kentucky counties
ABC 36 Storm Team
Alyssa Andrews -
September 14, 2020 0
Heavy showers and thunderstorms caused flash flooding issues across central Kentucky over the weekend. Rainfall totals from the Kentucky Mesonet at WKU show some...
Read more
Sports
SPORTS SECTIONSSports
36 Blitz
Solid Blue
High School Highlight Reel
LATEST SPORTS
SEC and ESPN/ABC reach milestone 10-year media agreement
athletics
Bryan Kennedy -
December 10, 2020 0
BIRMINGHAM, Alabama (December 10, 2020) - The Southeastern Conference and ESPN have finalized a milestone 10-year agreement that grants ABC and ESPN exclusive broadcast...
Read more
Student-Athlete of the Week: Avrey Rigney
athletics
Alyssa Andrews -
December 10, 2020 0
We head to Madison County to honor a freshman that’s already making a stamp on her varsity volleyball team.
Our student-athlete of the week is...
Read more
KHSAA votes to push back Boy’s/Girl’s Sweet 16, keep season start date
athletics
Bryan Kennedy -
December 10, 2020 0
LEXINGTON, KY (WTVQ) - The KHSAA Board of Control met on Thursday and another big decision was made regarding winter sports. The Board voted...
Read more
#1 Georgetown beats IU-Southeast, 82-72
athletics
Bryan Kennedy -
December 10, 2020 0
GEORGETOWN, Ky (GC Athletics) - Kyran Jones and Derrin Boyd helped to do the heavy lifting against a sharp-shooting IU Southeast team Wednesday. The...
Read more
Blair Green scores career high as No. 9 Kentucky rolls past Marshall
athletics
Bryan Kennedy -
December 9, 2020 0
LEXINGTON, Ky. (UK Athletics) – Junior Blair Green scored a career-high 17 points as the ninth-ranked Kentucky women's basketball team beat Marshall 79-45 on...
Read more
Lexington Legends no longer an affiliate of the Kansas City Royals
athletics
Bryan Kennedy -
December 9, 2020 0
LEXINGTON, KY (WTVQ) - The Lexington Legends are no longer the Single “A” Affiliate of the Kansas City Royals.
https://twitter.com/lexingtonlegend/status/1336718817523806214?s=21
The Royals moved their “A”...
Read more
Keeneland has 1,588 horses in January sale
Equestrian
Tom Kenny -
December 8, 2020 0
Keeneland will continue to offer online and phone bidding to enable buyers to participate in the January Sale remotely.
Read more
Keeneland catalogs 79 lots for December Digital Sale
Equestrian
Tom Kenny -
December 8, 2020 0
The sale will be held Tuesday, Dec. 15 as part of Keeneland’s Digital Sales Ring platform.
Read more
Contests
Lee & Hayley 12 Days of Giveaways
Student Athlete of the Week
Teacher of the Week
Cash for Holiday Gifts Giveaway
Golden Care Provider of Month
Community
WTVQ-TV Public Inspection File
The FCC (Federal Communications Commission) requires TV stations to maintain a public inspection file that contains documents relevant to the station’s operation and dealings with the community and the FCC. The contents of the public inspection file is listed below. Hyperlinks are provided for the reports the FCC require stations to post on their web sites.
Viewing the Public Inspection File: In addition to viewing some of our files online, you may view our complete file during normal business hours at the WTVQ-TV studio: 6940 Man O War Blvd., Lexington, KY 40511. Although you do not need to make an appointment, making one may be helpful to the station and to you. You may request, either in person or telephonically, copies of materials in the file which we will provide to you at a reasonable charge.
Contact Information:  Email: Public File Coordinator ; Phone: 859.294.6100.
Public File Contents
1. FCC License: Click here to access station broadcast licenses on the FCC website.
2. The Public and Broadcasting: This FCC-published manual describes the FCC and its regulations and provides information about what broadcast stations must do to comply with those regulations. Click here to access a copy.
3. Children’s Television Programming Reports (FCC Form 398): TV stations must prepare and retain in their files quarterly reports identifying the educational and informational programming for children aired by the station. Click here to view station reports on the FCC website.
4. Children’s Programming Commercial Limits: The FCC rules limit the type and amount of advertising that may be aired during TV programming directed to children 12 and under. Our public file contains compliance records.
5. EEO: The FCC requires TV stations to afford equal opportunity in employment. To this end, stations with five or more full-time employees must maintain records of its recruitment efforts and prepare an annual public file report listing specified information about its recruitment efforts. Click here to view our EEO Report.
6. Political File: This file contains information related to broadcast time purchased by or on behalf of a legally qualified candidate for public office; or (B) communicates a message relating to any political matter of national importance.
7. Applications and Related Materials: Stations are required to maintain, for public inspection, copies of all applications filed with the FCC. Click here to access our applications on the FCC website.
8. Quarterly Programming Reports
9. Ownership Reports: Click here to access our ownership reports on the FCC website.
Privacy Policy
ABC 36, WTVQ-TV, LLC and Morris Network, Inc and its affiliates and subsidiaries, which includes WTVQ-TV, LLC (collectively known as “Company”), strongly believes in maintaining the privacy of nonpublic information we collect from individuals who visit our web site (the “Website”). We want you to understand how and why we collect, use and disclose the personal information about you on our Website. This Privacy Policy provides you with information concerning our practices and procedures as they relate specifically to information we collect at the Website. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any information you may provide to us through other means; for example, at a live event, via mail, or via telephone. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully so that you understand our online privacy practices. By visiting this Website, you agree that your visit, and any dispute over our online privacy practices, is governed by this Privacy Policy. If you have additional questions or would like further information on this topic, please feel free to write to news36@wtvq.com. We may update our Privacy Policy periodically, so please check back here for the latest version of our Privacy Policy.
CHILDREN’S PRIVACY
We are strongly committed to preserving online privacy for all of our Website visitors, including children. This Website is a general audience site, and we do not knowingly collect information about children or sell products to children. Consistent with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, we will not knowingly collect any information from children under the age of 13, knowingly allow anyone under 13 to register with our Website or to provide any other personally identifying information. If you’re under 13, please do not provide us with any personally identifying information about yourself (such as your name, your email address or your phone number).
TYPES OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND USE ON THIS WEBSITE
The information we gather falls into two categories: (1) information (for example, your name and address) that you voluntarily supply when you register or initiate transactions, and (2) information gathered on usage patterns and preferences as visitors navigate through our sites, use our services such as free email, or read our email newsletters. In some cases, it is an agent or affiliate of ours that collects the information on our behalf. Third party providers featured on or linked to by our Website, such as vendors of products and services offered through our Website, may be gathering the same kinds of information. You are not required to provide any non-public personally identifiable information on this Website. We gather customer information you may volunteer when inquiring about our products and services or when using our products and services. New Vision and our business partners use this information only for the purposes of inquiry follow-up or for operational delivery of products and services. We do not collect any non-public personally identifiable information about you at our Website unless you choose to provide it to us voluntarily. We define “non-public personally identifiable information” as information that is unique to you or a third party and might include your name, phone number, company name, company address, insurance policy number, account username or password. If you encounter a window or page that requests information that you do not want to share with us, do not enter the information and do not proceed with that window or page. If you do provide us with non-public personally identifiable information, we will only use it for the purposes described where it is collected, and we will not sell, license, transmit or disclose this information outside of New Vision or its affiliates unless (1) you expressly authorize us to do so, (2) it is necessary to allow our trusted service providers or agents to provide services for us, (3) in order to provide our products or services to you, (4) it is disclosed to entities that perform marketing services on our behalf or to other entities with whom we have joint marketing agreements that obligate such entities to maintain the privacy of your non-public personally identifiable information, or (5) otherwise as we are required or permitted by law.
EMAIL
We appreciate your questions and comments about our Website, products and services and welcome your email messages to mailbox(es) listed on our Website. We will share your messages with those within our organization who are most capable of addressing the issues contained in your message. We will keep a copy of your message until we have had an opportunity to address your concerns. We may archive your message for a certain period of time or discard it, but your email address will not be used for any other purpose.
CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY
Security is a top priority at the Website. When you submit sensitive information to our Website, your information is protected both online and offline. We restrict access to non-public personally identifiable information collected about you at our Website to our employees, WTVQ-TV, LLC and our affiliates’ employees, or others who need to know that information to provide services to you or in the course of conducting our normal business operations. We maintain appropriate physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect non-public personally identifiable information. We protect our databases with various physical, technical and procedural measures and we restrict access to your information by unauthorized persons. We also advise all employees, service providers, agents and affiliates about their responsibility to protect customer data and we provide them with appropriate guidelines for adhering to our company’s business ethics standards and confidentiality policies.
REGISTRATION INFORMATION
To make use of certain features on our Website (such as to receive email newsletters, or post a classified ad), visitors need to register and to provide certain information as part of the registration process. We may also ask for information from those who buy products or services or conduct other transactions on our Website. (We may ask, for example, for your name, email address, gender, age, zip code or credit card number, and we might request information on your interest in sports, personal finance, the performing arts, and the like.) The information you supply will help us to offer you more personalized features, to tailor our Website to your interests and make them more useful to you, and to process e-commerce transactions that may be made available on our Website. The more you tell us about yourself, the more value we can offer you. Supplying such information is entirely voluntary. But if you don’t supply the information we need, we may be unable to provide you with services we make available to other visitors to our Website. For example, we can’t send you email alerting you to a new service we’re offering, or breaking news that may interest you if you don’t tell us what you’re interested in and give us your email address.
CONTESTS AND OTHER PROMOTIONS
From time to time, we may offer contests, sweepstakes or other promotions on our Website. If you enter one of these promotions, you’ll have to provide information about yourself (such as your name, address, telephone number and email address) so that we can contact you if you win. We may share this information with New Vision, our affiliates and with any co-sponsor of the promotion (we will identify any co-sponsor in the official rules for the promotion). If you don’t want us to collect the information requested in the registration form or to provide it to our affiliates or contest co-sponsors, please do not enter the contest or sweepstakes.
EMAIL NEWSLETTERS
We may also offer you the opportunity to subscribe to email newsletters on topics that we believe are of interest to our visitors. If you have opted to receive a particular newsletter, you may always unsubscribe later if you decide not to receive further mailings of the newsletter from us. See “Opting Out” below.
COOKIES
To help make our sites more responsive to the needs of our visitors, we use a standard feature of browser software, called a “cookie,” to assign each visitor a unique, random number, a sort of user ID, if you will, that resides on your computer. A cookie is a piece of information which a web server may place on your computer when you visit a website. Cookies are commonly used by websites to improve the user experience and have not been known to transmit computer viruses or otherwise harm your computer. Many cookies last only through a single website session, or visit. Others may have an expiration date, or may remain on your computer until you delete them. The cookie doesn’t actually identify the visitor, just the computer that a visitor uses to access our Website. Unless you voluntarily identify yourself (through registration, for example), we won’t know who you are, even if we assign a cookie to your computer. Our cookies do not gather non-public personally identifiable information. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply. A cookie can’t read unrelated data off your hard drive. Our advertisers and the third parties that provide products or services through our Website may also assign their own cookies to your browser, a process that we don’t control. We use cookies to help us tailor our Website to your needs, to deliver a better, more personalized service. For example, we use cookies to avoid showing you the same ad, repeatedly, during a single visit. In addition, we may use cookies to track the pages on our Website visited by our users. We can build a better Website if we know which pages our users are visiting and how often. Of course, you can set your browser not to accept cookies, but if you do, you may not be able to take advantage of the personalized features enjoyed by other visitors to our Website. We may occasionally use other companies to set cookies on our websites and gather cookie information for us. In some cases, we may also use another company to operate web servers or process credit card purchases for our website. We use the cookie information gathered by these companies in the same manner as stated above.
OTHER METHODS OF COLLECTING INFORMATION
Our web pages may contain electronic images (called “single-pixel GIFs” or “web beacons”) that allow us and our vendors to count users who have visited particular pages or to access certain cookies. We may use these tools and other technologies to recognize which pages users visit, and which links they click on. These features may also be included in our email newsletters so that we can learn which messages have been opened and acted upon. We may also be able to verify your online purchases from us or from third party sites that have agreed to share such information with us.
BROWSER LEVEL INFORMATION AND IP ADDRESSES
Our web servers automatically collect limited information about your computer configuration when you visit our Website, including the type of browser software you use, the operating system you’re running, the resolution of your computer monitor, the website that referred you, and your IP address. (Your IP address is a numerical address that is used by computers connected to the Internet to identify your computer so that data (such as the web pages you want to view) can be transmitted to you. We also use IP address information for systems administration and troubleshooting purposes. Your IP address does not tell us who you are.) We use this information to deliver our web pages to you upon request, to tailor our Website to the interests of our users, and to measure traffic within our Website.
THIRD PARTY ADVERTISING
The ads appearing on this Website are delivered to you by third party advertisers, our Web hosting partner,and sponsors. Information about your visits to this Website, such as number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or other personal in-formation), is used to serve ads to you.
THIRD PARTY COOKIES
In the course of serving advertisements to this Website, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.
DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION
We will not share non-public personally identifiable information you provide when registering on our Website with advertisers. We may, however, take the information you provide and aggregate it with data from all the other people that use this Website and associated services. Then we will use that pool of information to inform our advertisers about our audience without identifying you personally. Vendors and Service Providers To make our sites more valuable to our visitors, we may offer some features in conjunction with other providers (“Provider Partners”). Our chat, email newsletters, email services and online classifieds for example, may be made available through cooperative arrangements with providers that specialize in operating such services. In some instances, our Provider Partners will have the same access to your information as we do. Their use of the information will be subject to the terms of their respective privacy policies, which you can find on their websites. Our Affiliates We may share the information that we collect from you with our affiliates (including New Vision) so that we and they can provide you with products and services provided by these entities that we believe may be of interest to you.
STATISTICAL INFORMATION
Much of the information we collect is in the form of aggregated statistics, such as the traffic that visits various pages within our sites, and the habits and preferences of our audience. Such aggregated information does not include any information that would identify you personally. We may use such aggregated information and disclose it to third parties as we see fit.
SITES TO WHICH WE LINK
This Privacy Policy only address the use and disclosure of information we collects online through this Website, not information that may be collected through other sources. For useful information and/or your convenience, we may provide links to other websites and web pages that we do not control the content or privacy policy. Please carefully review the approach these sites take to your privacy before you use them or provide them with information. We cannot be responsible for the privacy or security practices of any websites or pages not under our control and we do not endorse any of these websites or pages, the services or products described or offered on such sites or pages, or any of the content contained on those sites or pages. We assume no liability for any unauthorized actions of third parties or accidental transmission errors that may disclose information about you, and we are not responsible for these other sites’ privacy practices, which may be different from our privacy practices.
OTHER DISCLOSURES
We may occasionally release information about our visitors when release is appropriate to comply with law, to enforce our Terms of Use, or to protect the rights, property or safety of visitors to our sites, the public, our customers, or our company and its employees, agents, partners and affiliates. As our business grows, we may buy or sell various assets. In the unlikely event that our company, or the bulk of our assets relating to this Website, is acquired by another company, information on our visitors would be among the transferred assets. Of course, any information that you include in a message that you post in any forum or other public posting area will be available to anyone with Internet access. If you don’t want people to know your name or email address, please do not include them in any message that you post publicly.
SHOPPING
For e-commerce transactions that may be made available on this Website, when you are ready to make a purchase on our Website, we will ask you to provide us with certain information, including your contact details (such as your name, address, telephone and email), and your billing information (such as your credit card number and the date that your card expires). We may also ask you to provide additional information such as unique identifiers (such as your date of birth), and registration information (login name and password). You will be able to review, update, or delete the information you have provided us (except, of course any information that we do not store) at any time by accessing your account on our Website. We will use the information you provide us to process your transaction and to contact you regarding your purchase if necessary. We will share this information with our Provider Partners to the extent necessary to facilitate your purchase (for purposes such as customer service, verification, fulfillment and billing purposes). We will not sell or rent your personal billing information to any third party. We may share non-financial information with our Provider Partners in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you consent (for example, by checking a box or by some other means), we will make your information available to third parties so that they, we, or both may contact you directly regarding special offers, promotions, products or services that may be of interest to you.
CREDIT CARD INFORMATION
We are very sensitive to the importance of our role in protecting the security of your transaction(s). Consequently, we use high grade encryption and the https security protocol to communicate with your browser software. This method is the industry standard security protocol, which makes it extremely difficult for anyone else to intercept the credit card information you send to us. Companies we work with to process credit card transactions also use high grade encryption and security protocols. Moreover, regular audits are conducted to ensure the privacy, security and appropriate processing of your information on our site.
RIGHT TO VERIFY THE ACCURACY OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT
If you register with our Website, you will have the opportunity to review, update, or delete the information you have provided us at any time (except, of course, any information that we do not store). Keeping your information accurate and up to date is important to us. Once you register, you can review your account information at anytime, by clicking on the login link on the Website. If you have questions about your account or would like to modify your account or information, please contact us by email at news36@wtvq.com . If you remove your registration information completely, you may not be able to continue using certain services that require registration (such as free email).
OPTING OUT
You agree that we may use your information to contact you for customer service, to inform you of important changes or additions to our Website or the services offered over our Website and to send you administrative notices or any communications relevant to your use of our Website. If you do not wish to receive these notices, please do not register with this Website. If you have subscribed to one of our email newsletters, you will always have the opportunity to unsubscribe from future mailings (for example, by clicking on an unsubscribe link in an email newsletter or by going back to our Website). Your email address will be removed from our email list. Please allow us a reasonable period of time in order to satisfy your request. If you have submitted your information on a page provided in conjunction with one of our Provider Partners, the information you submit may be jointly maintained by us and the Provider Partner. If you decide to opt out on our Website, you may also need to contact the Provider Partner separately to request the Provider Partner to remove your information from its database.
STORAGE OF INFORMATION
All information gathered on our Website is stored within a database operated by us or by a contractor on our behalf. Sensitive information, such as your password is encoded for storage. For e-commerce transactions that may be made available on our Website, in certain instances we may transmit your billing information using encryption. Encryption scrambles your credit card number and personal information. However, as effective as encryption technology is, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information you supply won’t be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet.
CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY
We may change this Website Privacy Policy at any time and from time to time. The most recent version of the Website Privacy Policy is reflected by the version date located at the bottom of this Website Privacy Policy. This Website Privacy Policy is not intended to and does not create any contractual or other legal right in or on behalf of any party.
CONTACTING US
If you have any questions about this Website Privacy Policy or would like to learn more about how we protect privacy, please write to us at ABC 36 WTVQ-TV, LLC 6940 Man O War Blvd Lexington KY 40509 or email to news36@wtvq.com
Terms Of Use
TERMS OF USE AGREEMENT This Internet Web site is owned and managed by Morris Network, Inc and this station (collectively “WTVQ-TV, LLC”, “we” or “us”). We provide this Web site and related services for your personal non-commercial use only and subject to your compliance with the provisions of this Terms of Use Agreement (the “Agreement”). Please read this Agreement carefully. Your use of our Web site means that you agree to be bound by this Agreement. If at any time you do not accept all the provisions of this Agreement you may not use this Web site.
Certain products, services, or content available on this Web site may be governed by additional terms, which are posted in connection with those products, services and content. You must agree to these additional terms before using those areas. In the event of an irreconcilable inconsistency between any such additional terms and this Agreement, the additional terms shall control.
YOU MAY NOT USE THIS WEBSITE FOR ANY PURPOSE THAT IS UNLAWFUL OR PROHIBITED BY THIS AGREEMENT AND/OR ANY APPLICABLE ADDITIONAL TERMS. YOUR ACCESS TO THIS WEBSITE MAY BE TERMINATED IMMEDIATELY IN OUR SOLE DISCRETION, WITH OR WITHOUT NOTICE, IF YOU FAIL TO COMPLY WITH ANY PROVISIONS OF THIS AGREEMENT AND/OR ANY APPLICABLE ADDITIONAL TERMS OR FOR NO REASON.
Changes to this Agreement
This Agreement is effective as of March 14, 2008. We reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to modify, alter, or otherwise change this Agreement and/or any additional terms at any time, and such modifications, alterations, or other changes will be effective upon posting by us to this Web site. We will provide notice of such change on this Web site. Your continued use of this Web site constitutes your acceptance and agreement to be bound by these changes. If at any time you do not accept these changes, you must discontinue use of this Web site.
General Use of the Web Site
The content on this Web site, except User Submissions (as defined below), including without limitation, the articles, other text, photographs, images, illustrations, graphics, software, scripts, sounds, music, videos, interactive features and the trademarks, service marks and logos contained therein (“Content”), are owned by or licensed to WTVQ. Content on the Web site is provided to you AS IS for your information and personal use only and may not be downloaded, copied, reproduced, distributed, transmitted, broadcast, displayed, sold, licensed, or otherwise exploited for any other purposes whatsoever without the prior written consent of WTVQ. WTVQ reserves all rights not expressly granted in and to the Web site and the Content.
You agree not to use the Web site, for any commercial use, without prior written authorization of WTVQ.
You may inquire about obtaining consent by writing:
WTVQ
Associated Press
Associated Press text, photo, graphic, audio/or video material shall not be published, broadcast, rewritten for broadcast or publication or redistributed directly or indirectly in any medium. Neither these AP materials nor any portion thereof may be stored in a computer except for personal use. AP will not be held liable for any delays, inaccuracies, errors or omissions therefrom or in the transmission or delivery of all or any part thereof or for any damages arising from any of the foregoing.
User Submissions As a WTVQ account holder you may submit video, text, files, images, photos, sounds or other materials (“User Submissions”). You understand that whether or not such User Submissions are published, WTVQ does not guarantee any confidentiality with respect to any User Submissions.
You shall be solely responsible for your own User Submissions and the consequences of posting or publishing them. In connection with User Submissions, you affirm, represent, and/or warrant that: you own or have the necessary licenses, rights, consents, and permissions to use and authorize WTVQ to use all patent, trademark, trade secret, copyright or other proprietary rights in and to any and all User Submissions to enable inclusion and use of the User Submissions in the manner contemplated by the Web site and these Terms of Use.
For clarity, you retain all of your ownership rights in your User Submissions. However, by submitting User Submissions to WTVQ, you hereby grant WTVQ a worldwide, non-exclusive, royalty-free, sublicenseable and transferable license to use, reproduce, distribute, prepare derivative works of, display, and perform the User Submissions in connection with the WTVQ Web site and WTVQ (and its successors’ and affiliates’) business, including without limitation for promoting and redistributing part or all of the WTVQ Web site (and derivative works thereof) in any media formats and through any media channels. You also hereby grant each user of the WTVQ Web site a non-exclusive license to access your User Submissions through the Web site, and to use, reproduce, distribute, display and perform such User Submissions as permitted through the functionality of the Web site and under these Terms of Service. The above licenses granted by you in User Videos terminate within a commercially reasonable time after you remove or delete your User Videos from the WTVQ Web site service. You understand and agree, however, that WTVQ may retain, but not display, distribute, or perform, server copies of User Submissions that have been removed or deleted. The above licenses granted by you in User Comments are perpetual and irrevocable.
In connection with User Submissions, you further agree that you will not submit material that is copyrighted, protected by trade secret or otherwise subject to third party proprietary rights, including privacy and publicity rights, unless you are the owner of such rights or have permission from their rightful owner to post the material and to grant WTVQ all of the license rights granted herein.
You further agree that you will not, in connection with User Submissions, submit material that is contrary to applicable local, national, and international laws and regulations.
WTVQ does not endorse any User Submission or any opinion, recommendation, or advice expressed therein, and WTVQ expressly disclaims any and all liability in connection with User Submissions. WTVQ does not permit copyright infringing activities and infringement of intellectual property rights on its Web site, and WTVQ will remove all Content and User Submissions if properly notified that such Content or User Submission infringes on another’s intellectual property rights. WTVQ reserves the right to remove Content and User Submissions without prior notice.
Additional Terms of Use
In addition to the general restrictions above, the following restrictions and conditions apply specifically to your use of Content on the WTVQ Web site.
You agree not to alter or modify any part of the Web site, including but not limited to WTVQ embeddable player or any other related technologies.
You agree not to access User Submissions or WTVQ Content through any technology or means other than the video playback pages of the web site itself, the WTVQ embedded player, or other explicitly authorized means WTVQ may designate.
If you use the WTVQ embedded player on your Web site, you must include a prominent link back to the WTVQ Web site including the pages containing the embedded player and you may not modify, build upon, or block any portion of the embedded player in any way.
If you use the WTVQ Uploader, you agree that it may automatically download and install updates from time to time from WTVQ. These updates are designed to improve, enhance and further develop the Uploader and may take the form of bug fixes, enhanced functions, new software modules and completely new versions. You agree to receive such updates (and permit WTVQ to deliver these to you) as part of your use of the Uploader.
You agree not to use or launch any automated system, including without limitation, “robots,” “spiders,” or “offline readers,” that accesses the Web site in a manner that sends more request messages to the WTVQ servers in a given period of time than a human can reasonably produce in the same period by using a conventional on-line web browser. Notwithstanding the foregoing, WTVQ grants the operators of public search engines permission to use spiders to copy materials from the site for the sole purpose of and solely to the extent necessary for creating publicly available searchable indices of the materials, but not caches or archives of such materials. WTVQ reserves the right to revoke these exceptions either generally or in specific cases. You agree not to collect or harvest any personally identifiable information, including account names, from the Web site, nor to use the communication systems provided by the Web site (e.g. comments, email) for any commercial solicitation purposes. You agree not to solicit, for commercial purposes, any users of the Web site with respect to their User Submissions.
You may access User Submissions solely:
? for your information and personal use;
? as intended through the normal functionality of the WTVQ Web site service; and
? for Streaming.
“Streaming” means a contemporaneous digital transmission of an audiovisual work via the Internet from the WTVQ Web site to a user’s device in such a manner that the data is intended for real-time viewing and not intended to be copied, stored, permanently downloaded, or redistributed by the user. Accessing User Videos for any purpose or in any manner other than Streaming is expressly prohibited. User Videos are made available “as is.”
User Comments are made available to you for your information and personal use solely as intended through the normal functionality of the WTVQ Web site service. User Comments are made available “as is”, and may not be used, copied, reproduced, distributed, transmitted, broadcast, displayed, sold, licensed, downloaded, or otherwise exploited in any manner not intended by the normal functionality of the WTVQ Web site service or otherwise as prohibited under this Agreement.
You may access WTVQ Content, User Submissions and other content only as permitted under this Agreement. WTVQ reserves all rights not expressly granted in and to the Content and the WTVQ Web site service.
You agree to not engage in the use, copying, or distribution of any of the Content other than expressly permitted herein, including any use, copying, or distribution of User Submissions of third parties obtained through the Web site for any commercial purposes. You agree not to circumvent, disable or otherwise interfere with security-related features of the WTVQ Web site or features that prevent or restrict use or copying of any Content or enforce limitations on use of the WTVQ Web site or the Content therein.
You understand that when using the WTVQ Web site, you will be exposed to User Submissions from a variety of sources, and that WTVQ is not responsible for the accuracy, usefulness, safety, or intellectual property rights of or relating to such User Submissions. You further understand and acknowledge that you may be exposed to User Submissions that are inaccurate, offensive, indecent, or objectionable, and you agree to waive, and hereby do waive, any legal or equitable rights or remedies you have or may have against WTVQ with respect thereto, and agree to indemnify and hold WTVQ, its Owners/Operators, affiliates, and/or licensors, harmless to the fullest extent allowed by law regarding all matters related to your use of the site.
Accounts, Security, Passwords
If the Web site requires you to open an account, you must complete the specified registration process by providing complete and accurate information as requested by the applicable online registration form. You are responsible for maintaining the completeness and accuracy of your registration data and any loss caused by your failure to do so is your responsibility. After you have completed the registration form, you may be asked to choose a password and a user name. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your password and account. You are responsible for any and all activities that occur under your account. We are not liable for any loss that you may incur as a result of someone else using your password or account, either with or without your knowledge. You may cancel your account by delivering notice in the manner provided in the additional terms applicable to the Web site feature for which you are registered.
Privacy and Protection of Personal Information
We have developed a Privacy Statement in order to inform you of our practices with respect to the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information. You can find this Statement by clicking here.
Fees
Except where otherwise provided, access to and use of this Web site are currently available without charge. We reserve the right to charge a fee for access to or use of this Web site at any time in the future. Your access to or use of this Web site before such time does not entitle you to use of this Web site without charge in the future.
Termination
WTVQ reserve the right, in its sole discretion, to modify, suspend, or terminate this Web site and/or any portion thereof, and/or your account or password, at any time for any reason with or without notice to you. We may immediately terminate these terms of use with respect to you (including your access to the Web site) without cause and without notice to you in our sole discretion. Upon termination, you must cease use of the Web site and destroy all materials obtained from such sites and all copies thereof whether made under these terms of use or otherwise. In the event of termination, you will still be bound by your obligations under this Agreement, including the warranties made by you, and by the disclaimers and limitations of liability. Additionally, we shall not be liable to you or any third-party for any termination of your access.
WTVQ reserves the right to decide whether Content or a User Submission is appropriate and complies with these Terms of Service for violations other than copyright infringement, such as, but not limited to, pornography, obscene or defamatory material, or excessive length. WTVQ may remove such User Submissions and/or terminate a User’s access for uploading such material in violation of these Terms of Service at any time, without prior notice and at its sole discretion.
Disclaimer of Warranties
YOUR USE OF, AND RELIANCE ON, ANY ADVICE OR INFORMATION OBTAINED FROM OR THROUGH THIS WEBSITE IS AT YOUR OWN RISK. ALL CONTENT, INCLUDING SOFTWARE, PRODUCTS, SERVICES, INFORMATION, TEXT AND RELATED GRAPHICS CONTAINED WITHIN OR AVAILABLE THROUGH THIS WEBSITE ARE PROVIDED TO YOU ON AN “AS IS,” “AS AVAILABLE” BASIS. WE MAKE NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, AS TO THE OPERATION OF THIS WEBSITE OR THE INFORMATION, CONTENT OR MATERIALS INCLUDED ON THIS WEBSITE. TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMISSIBLE PURSUANT TO APPLICABLE LAW, WE DISCLAIM ALL REPRESENTATIONS AND WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR SATISFACTORY QUALITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, WORKMANLIKE EFFORT, INFORMATIONAL CONTENT, TITLE, OR NON-INFRINGEMENT OF THE RIGHTS OF THIRD PARTIES. WE DO NOT WARRANT OR MAKE ANY REPRESENTATIONS THAT THIS WEBSITE WILL OPERATE ERROR-FREE OR UNINTERRUPTED, THAT DEFECTS WILL BE CORRECTED, OR THAT THIS WEBSITE AND/OR ITS SERVER WILL BE FREE OF VIRUSES AND/OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS. WE DO NOT WARRANT OR MAKE ANY REPRESENTATIONS REGARDING SUITABILITY, AVAILABILITY, ACCURACY, RELIABILITY, COMPLETENESS, OR TIMELINESS OF ANY MATERIAL OF ANY KIND CONTAINED WITHIN THIS WEBSITE FOR ANY PURPOSE. WE ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY FAILURES CAUSED BY SERVER ERRORS, MISDIRECTED OR REDIRECTED TRANSMISSIONS, FAILED INTERNET CONNECTIONS, INTERRUPTIONS IN THE TRANSMISSION OR RECEIPT OF TICKET ORDERS OR INTERACTIVE SERVICES, OR ANY COMPUTER VIRUS OR OTHER TECHNICAL DEFECT, WHETHER HUMAN OR TECHNICAL IN NATURE.
Limitations on Liability
In no event shall WTVQ, this station, their subsidiaries, affiliates, distributors, suppliers, licensors, agents or others involved in creating, sponsoring, promoting, or otherwise making available this Web site and its contents, be liable to any person or entity whatsoever for any direct, indirect, incidental, special, compensatory, consequential, or punitive damages or any damages whatsoever, including but not limited to: (i) loss of goodwill, profits, business interruption, data or other intangible losses; (ii) your inability to use, unauthorized use of, performance or non-performance of this Web site; (iii) unauthorized access to or tampering with your personal information or transmissions; (iv) the provision or failure to provide any service; (v) errors or inaccuracies contained on this Web site or any information, software, products, services, and related graphics obtained through this Web site; (vi) any transactions entered into through this Web site; (vii) any property damage including damage to your computer or computer system caused by viruses or other harmful components, during or on account of access to or use of this Web site or any site to which it provides hyperlinks; or (viii) damages otherwise arising out of the use of this Web site and our Internet Services. The limitations of liability shall apply regardless of the form of action, whether based on contract, tort, negligence, strict liability or otherwise, even if we have been advised of the possibility of damages.
Indemnification
You agree to indemnify, defend, and hold harmless WTVQ, this station, their subsidiaries, agents, distributors and affiliates, and their officers, directors and employees from and against any and all claims, demands, liabilities, losses, expenses, damages, and costs, including reasonable attorneys? fees, resulting from your violation of any provision of this Agreement, any additional terms, the Privacy Statement, or any warranty you provide herein, or otherwise arising in any way out of your use of this Web site. We reserve the right to take exclusive control and defense of any such claim otherwise subject to indemnification by you, in which event you will provide us with such cooperation as is reasonably requested by us.
Links
This Web site may contain links to websites operated by third parties. We do not monitor or control the linked sites and make no representations regarding, and are not liable or responsible for the accuracy, completeness, timeliness, reliability or availability of, any of the content available at these sites. If you choose to access any third party site, you do so at your own risk. The presence of a link to a third-party site does not constitute or imply WTVQ’s or this station?s endorsement, sponsorship, or recommendation of the third party or of the content, products, or services contained on, or available through, the site.
Third-Party Merchants
This Web site may enable you to order and receive products, information and services from businesses that are not owned or operated by us. The purchase, payment, warranty, delivery, maintenance, and all other matters concerning the merchandise, services, information or advice ordered or received from such businesses are solely between you and such businesses. We do not endorse, warrant, or guarantee such products, information, or services, and are not liable for the accuracy, completeness, or usefulness of such information or the quality of availability of such products or services. We will not be a party to or in any way responsible for monitoring any transaction between you and third-party providers of such products, services, or information, or for ensuring the confidentiality of your credit card information. Any charges or obligations you incur in your dealings with these third parties are your responsibility.
Terms of Sale
By placing an order through the Web site, you make an offer to purchase the selected voucher, product and/or merchandise. For gift certificate purchases, your purchase is redeemable for goods or services by the seller of such goods and services (hereinafter referred to as ?Merchant?). The Merchant, not WTVQ, is the seller of the goods and services and is solely responsible for redeeming any gift certificate purchased on the Web site. WTVQ sells a voucher that can be redeemed in connection with your purchase of goods or services from Merchant, however, it is the sole responsibility of Merchant to comply with all rules and regulations pertaining to certificate redemption. WTVQ expressly waives any and all liability for injuries, illnesses, damages, claims, liabilities and costs associated, in any respect, with the voucher. The issuing of credit or payout on the balance of the gift certificate, if any, is at the sole discretion of the Merchant, unless otherwise required by law. The gift certificate expires on the date specified on the certificate, unless otherwise prohibited by law. Additional restrictions may apply. Software And Downloads Available Through This Web site Any software that is made available to view and/ or download in connection with this Web site, including podcasts, audio streaming, or video streaming, is owned or controlled by us and/or our licensors, affiliates and suppliers and is protected by copyright laws and international treaty provisions. Your use of such software is limited to private, non-commercial use and is also governed by the terms of the end user license agreement, if any, which accompanies or is included with the software. We accept no responsibility or liability in connection with any software owned or controlled by third parties.
Interactive Services
This Web site may offer certain interactive components such as bulletin boards, chat rooms, blogs, and forums (collectively “Interactive Services”). Additional terms may cover these services, which appear on the pages where these services are available and can be found here.
Subscription Services
This Web site may offer certain subscription services such as newsletters and Real Simple Syndication (“RSS”) feeds (collectively “Subscription Services”). By registering for a Subscription Service, you will be subject to any charges and additional terms set forth in the description of that service.
Premium Services
This Web site may offer certain Interactive Services and Subscription Services conditioned on your payment of a fee (“Premium Service”). By using the Premium Service, you will be subject to any charges and rules set forth in the additional terms for that service, which appear on the ages where such services are available. A copy of Premium Service additional terms can be found here.
Contests/Sweepstakes
For additional terms applying to all contests or sweepstakes conducted by this Web site, refer to this site’s contest or sweepstakes information.
Governing Law
This Agreement shall be governed by the laws of the State of WTVQ, as it is applied to agreements entered into and to be performed entirely within such state, without regard to conflict of law principles. You agree that any cause of action you, WTVQ, or this station brings to enforce this Agreement or in connection with any matters related to this Web site and/or the Privacy Statement shall be brought only in either the state or Federal courts located in WTVQ. You consent to the personal jurisdiction of the courts of the State of WTVQ for any cause of action arising out of this Agreement. You agree to file any cause of action with respect to this Agreement within one year after the cause of action arises, and that a cause of action filed after this date is barred.
Severability
If any provision of this Agreement, or the application thereof to any person or circumstances, is held invalid or for any reason unenforceable including, but not limited to, the warranty disclaimers and liability limitations, then such provision shall be deemed superseded by a valid, enforceable provision that matches, as closely as possible, the original provision, and the other provisions of this Agreement shall remain in full force and effect. The failure of either party to insist upon strict performance of any provision of this Agreement shall not be construed as a waiver of any provision or right. Unless expressly provided otherwise, this Agreement is the entire agreement between you and us with respect to the use of this Web site and shall not be modified except in writing, signed by an authorized representative of WTVQ.
Contact Us
If you have any questions or comments regarding this Agreement, the Privacy Statement, the practices of this Web site, or your dealings with this Web site, you may send them by email to WTVQ You must send any official correspondence via postal mail to:
WTVQ
Please include the web address, call letters or station’s name. Please note that this email address should only be used for specific technical issues related to the website such as unsubscribing from a database. The recipients of these emails will not be able, in general to answer concerns regarding on-air programming, promotions or other non-web related issues.
Foreign Users
This Web site is governed by and operated in accordance with the laws of United States of America and is intended for enjoyment of residents of the United States. We make no representation that this website is governed by or operated in accordance with the laws of other nations. By using this site and submitting any personal information, visitors from outside of the United States acknowledge the this site is subject to U.S. law, consent to the transfer of personal data to the U.S., and waive any claims that may arise under their own national laws.
Copyright & Trademark Notice
Use of Intellectual Property
This Web site, and all of its Contents, are protected by copyright, trademark and other laws of the United States, as well as international conventions and the laws of other countries. The Content is owned or controlled by us or by other parties that have provided rights thereto to us. This Web site is protected by copyright as a collective work or compilation under the copyright laws of the United States and other countries, and all individual articles, content, and other elements comprising this Web site are also copyrighted works. Content on the Web site may not be downloaded, copied, reproduced, distributed, transmitted, broadcast, displayed, sold, licensed, or otherwise exploited for any other purposes whatsoever without the prior written consent of WTVQ.
Other trademarks, service marks, product names and company names or logos appearing on this Web site that are not owned by us may not be used without express permission from their owners.
Additionally, unless otherwise expressly permitted in writing, we explicitly disclaim any responsibility for the accuracy, completeness or availability of information, content and materials found on sites that link to or from any page beyond the homepage of this Web site.
You may inquire about obtaining permission by writing:
WTVQ
Digital Millennium Copyright Act We respect the intellectual property rights of third parties, and comply with the terms of the Digital Millennium Copyright Act (DMCA) regarding such rights. By submitting any material or photographs through this Web site, you are granting permission to have this material posted on this Web site, and are representing that you are the rightful owner of the submitted material, and that no one else may claim rights to this material. We reserve the right to remove access to infringing material. Such actions do not affect or modify any other rights we may have under law or contract. You can find our procedures for providing notice of alleged copyright infringement here. We will terminate the accounts of users who repeatedly infringe third party rights.
Procedure for Making Claim of Copyright Infringement If you believe that your work has been copied in a way that constitutes copyright infringement, you should send written notification thereof, in accordance with the provisions of the Digital Millennium Copyright Act, to our Designated Agent, who can be reached as follows:
By mail:
WTVQ
Pursuant to 17 U.S.C. ? 512(c), to be effective, the Notification must include the following:
(i) A physical or electronic signature of a person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.
(ii) Identification of the copyrighted work claimed to have been infringed, or, if multiple copyrighted works at a single online site are covered by a single notification, a representative list of such works at that site.
(iii) Identification of the material that is claimed to be infringing or to be the subject of infringing activity and that is to be removed or access to which is to be disabled, and information reasonably sufficient to permit WTVQ to locate the material.
(iv) Information reasonably sufficient to permit WTVQ to contact the complaining party, such as an address, telephone number, and, if available, an email address.
(v) A statement that the complaining party has a good faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law.
(vi) A statement that the information in the notification is accurate, and under penalty of perjury, that the complaining party is authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.
This process only relates to reporting a claim of copyright infringement. Messages related to other matters will not receive a response through this process.
You acknowledge that if you fail to comply with all of the requirements of this Section, your Claim may not be valid.
Counter-Notice. If you believe that your User Submission that was removed (or to which access was disabled) is not infringing, or that you have the authorization from the copyright owner, the copyright owner’s agent, or pursuant to the law, to post and use the content in your User Submission, you may send a counter-notice containing the following information to the Copyright Agent:
– Your physical or electronic signature;
– Identification of the content that has been removed or to which access has been disabled and the location at which the content appeared before it was removed or disabled;
– A statement that you have a good faith belief that the content was removed or disabled as a result of mistake or a misidentification of the content; and
– Your name, address, telephone number, and e-mail address, a statement that you consent to the jurisdiction of the state of Delaware, and a statement that you will accept service of process from the person who provided notification of the alleged infringement.
If a counter-notice is received by the Copyright Agent, WTVQ may send a copy of the counter-notice to the original complaining party informing that person that it may replace the removed content or cease disabling it in 10 business days. Unless the copyright owner files an action seeking a court order against the content provider, member or user, the removed content may be replaced, or access to it restored, in 10 to 14 business days or more after receipt of the counter-notice, at WTVQ?s sole discretion.
Seek It Local Free Classifieds Terms and Conditions
Seek It Local Free Classifieds (the “Service”) is provided to you by WTVQ Television LLC and this station (“we” or “us”). The Service is provided subject to this Web site?s Terms of Use Agreement, Copyright & Trademark Notice and Privacy Statement, as supplemented by this Web site?s Interactive Services Additional Terms and these Seek It Local Free Classified terms and conditions (collectively “Service Terms”). By using these Seek It Local Free Classifieds, you agree to abide by these Service Terms. We reserve the right to deny access to this website to anyone who violates these Service Terms or who, in our judgment, interferes with the ability of others to enjoy the Web site, or infringes the rights of others. A. Your Use of the Service
1. Personal Responsibility.
You must post ads using your real name and your real e-mail address. You are responsible for all statements made or materials posted under your name, including liability for harm caused by such statements or materials. You may not transfer, sell, or otherwise assign your rights or obligations under this Agreement.
2. Posting Listings.
You or your group may post one advertisement for an item or service per day in each of the three sections of the site. Thus, you are limited to a total of three advertisements per day for each item or service. Multiple people posting for the same item or service (i.e., business partners) will be considered a group. Advertisements will remain on the Service for five days. Please proofread your ads carefully, as we cannot delete an ad because it contains a mistake or because an item has sold.
3. Categories.
You must post advertisements only in categories that are relevant to the item or service that you are advertising. We reserve the right (but do not assume the obligation) to edit, reclassify, revise, or cancel any advertisement at any time. 4. Prohibited Postings.
You are prohibited from posting material that: (i) contains offensive, vulgar, profane, false, abusive, libelous, hateful, defamatory or obscene language; (ii) contains fraudulent, deceptive, or misleading statements; (iii) violates a copyright or trademark, or any other intellectual property right of another; (iv) violates the privacy rights of any third party; or (v) violates any municipal, state or federal law, rule, regulation or ordinance, or attempts to encourage such violation. Use of the Service is limited to individuals interested in buying, selling, and trading goods and services, and is not intended for personal correspondence, discussions, or commentary. Please click here to visit our free discussion forums. You are prohibited from posting or otherwise making available content of the following types:
(a) Adult-oriented material
(b) Advice or admonishments
(c) Affidavits
(d) Airline tickets that restrict transfer
(e) Alcohol products
(f) Alerts
(g) Animal parts
(h) Announcements
(i) Blood, bodily fluids, or body parts
(j) Bulk email or mailing lists that contain names, addresses, phone numbers, or other personal identifying information
(k) Burglary tools, such as lock-picks or motor vehicle master keys
(l) Calendar items or events (including classes and seminars)
(m) Calls for action
(n) Comments about other ads or posters
(o) Controlled substances or illegal drugs, substances and items used to manufacture controlled substances and drug paraphernalia
(p) Counterfeit currency, coins and stamps, as well as equipment designed to make them
(q) Counterfeit or knock-off brand name goods
(r) Discussions
(s) Donation requests/solicitations
(t) Competing Web sites
(u) Concert and event tickets
(v) Employment
(w) Endorsements
(x) False identification cards, items with police insignia, citizenship documents, or birth certificates
(y) File sharing / piracy
(z) Fireworks, including “safe and sane” fireworks or any destructive devices or explosives
(aa) Fundraisers
(bb) Gambling items, such as lottery tickets, sports trading cards “grab bags,” raffle tickets, sweepstakes entries, or slot machines
(cc) Host families for exchange students
(dd) Illegal telecommunications equipment, such as access cards, password sniffers, access card programmers and unloopers, or cable descramblers
(ee) Material the infringes copyright such as warez, bootlegs, etc.
(ff) Medical paraphernalia (syringes, insulin pumps, catheters, etc.)
(gg) Medications of any kind (including supplements)
(hh) Monetary requests
(ii) Non-packaged food items or adulterated food
(jj) Notes that an item has sold
(kk) Other sites with free classifieds
(ll) Personal correspondence
(mm) Personal opinions or expressions
(nn) Pesticides or hazardous substances, or items containing hazardous substances or material containing toxic substances without a warning label
(oo) Pet ads not related to the buying and selling of pet companions
(pp) Prescription medication
(qq) Replies to others ads or posters
(rr) Restricted or regulated plants and insects, or live insects or pests
(ss) Rescue facilities
(uu) Stolen property or personal property with the serial number removed or altered
(vv) Thank-you notes
(ww) Tobacco
(xx) Stories of personal experiences
(yy) Used bedding, unless sanitized in accordance with law
(zz) Used or rebuilt batteries, or batteries containing mercury
(aaa) Warnings
(bbb) Weapons and related items, including firearms, disguised, undetectable or switchblade knives, martial arts weapons, sniper scopes, silencers, ammunition, large capacity magazines, BB guns, tear gas or stun guns
(ccc) Web addresses or Web sites.
We reserve the right to remove any Content posted on the Service and/or terminate your access to the Service at any time for any reason.
5. Prohibited Use.
You may not use the Service to harvest or otherwise collect names, e-mail addresses or other identifying information from other participants.
6. Content License.
When you post messages, text, files, images, photos, video, sounds, or other materials (“Content”) on the Service, you are representing that you are the owner of the material, or are making your submission with the express consent of the owner. By submitting material to the Service, you agree that we may reproduce, modify, and distribute such material as we see fit in any medium and for any purpose. You also agree that we may identify you as the author of any of your postings by name, email address or screen name as we see appropriate.
B. Disclaimers
7. Content.
Content posted on, transmitted through, or linked from the Service, is the sole responsibility of the person from whom such Content originated. You are entirely responsible for all Content that you post, email or otherwise make available via the Service. WTVQ and this station do not control, and are not responsible for, Content made available through the Service.
8. Third Parties.
You understand that we are not involved in the actual transaction between buyers and sellers. As a result, we have no control over the quality, safety or legality of the items advertised, the truth or accuracy of the listings, the ability of sellers to sell items or the ability of buyers to pay for items. In addition, we cannot ensure that a buyer or seller will actually complete a transaction. Your interactions with organizations and/or individuals found on or through the Service, including payment and delivery of goods or services, and any other terms, conditions, warranties or representations associated with such dealings, are solely between you and such organizations and/or individuals. You agree that this Web site shall not be responsible or liable for any loss or damage of any sort incurred as the result of any such dealings. If there is a dispute between participants on this site, or between users and any third party, you understand and agree that this Web site is under no obligation to become involved. In the event that you have a dispute with one or more other users, you hereby release this Web site, its parent and affiliates and their directors, officers, managers, employees, shareholders, agents, and licensors from claims, demands and damages (actual and consequential) of every kind or nature, known or unknown, suspected and unsuspected, disclosed and undisclosed, arising out of or in any way related to such disputes and/or our service. If you are a California resident, you agree to waive California Civil Code Section 1542, which says: “A general release does not extend to claims which the creditor does not know or suspect to exist in his favor at the time of executing the release, which, if known by him must have materially affected his settlement with the debtor.”
9. Use At Your Own Risk.
This Web site does not pre-screen or approve Content, but this Web site reserves the right (but not the obligation) in its sole discretion to refuse, delete or move any Content that is available via the Service, for violating the letter or spirit of the Agreement or for any other reason. We do not and cannot review every posting, verify the accuracy of statements made by participants, or determine whether the materials posted by participants violate the rights of others. WE ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY STATEMENTS OR MATERIALS POSTED ON THIS SITE. Use caution as scam artists may attempt to take advantage of users of the Service ? BUYER BEWARE.
C. Miscellaneous
10. No Agency.
You and this station are independent contractors, and no agency, partnership, joint venture, employee-employer or franchiser-franchisee relationship is intended or created by this Service.
Interactive Service Additional Terms
You may participate in the Interactive Service by reading and agreeing to the Terms of Use Agreement and these Interactive Service Additional Terms, and by completing the registration form where one is provided. If you do not agree to abide by the Terms of Use Agreement and these Interactive Service Additional Terms, you may not participate in the Interactive Service.
You agree that you will not:
? Deliver any unsolicited advertisement, promotional materials, junk email, bulk email (also known as “spam”), chain letters, surveys or contests, or solicit participation in any pyramid schemes (unless it is on a page that explicitly states that such postings are allowed on that page).
? Deliver any unlawful (according to local, state, federal, or international law or regulation) postings to or through this Web site, or any postings which advocate illegal activity.
? Deliver, or provide links to, any postings containing material that could be considered harmful, obscene, pornographic, indecent, lewd, violent, abusive, profane, insulting, threatening, harassing, hateful or otherwise objectionable.
? Deliver, or provide links to, any postings containing material that harasses, victimizes, degrades, or intimidates an individual or group of individuals on the basis of religion, race, ethnicity, sexual orientation, gender, age, or disability.
? Deliver, or provide links to, any postings containing defamatory, false or libelous material.
? Deliver, or provide links to, any posting that infringes or violates any intellectual property or other right of any entity or person, including, without limitation, copyrights, patents, trademarks, laws governing trade secrets, rights to privacy, or publicity.
? Deliver any posting to that you do not have a right to make available under law or contractual or fiduciary relationships.
? Impersonate another person or entity or falsely state or otherwise misrepresent your affiliation with a person or entity, or adopt a false identity if the purpose of doing so is to mislead, deceive, or defraud another.
? Manipulate identifiers, including by forging headers, in order to disguise the origin of any posting that you deliver.
? Use the Interactive Service in any manner which could damage, disable, overburden, or impair or otherwise interfere with the use of this Web site or other users’ computer equipment, or cause damage, disruption or limit the functioning of any software, hardware, or telecommunications equipment, including by means of uploading or transmitting to this Web site or WTVQ?s or this station?s servers any computer viruses, Trojan horses, worms, or other disabling or harmful software intended to damage, interfere with, intercept or monitor surreptitiously, or take over another computer.
? Attempt to gain unauthorized access to this Web site, any related website, other accounts, computer system, or networks connected to this Web site, through hacking, password mining, or any other means.
? Obtain or attempt to obtain any materials or information through any means not intentionally made available through this Web site, including harvesting or otherwise collecting information about others, such as email addresses.
You are solely responsible and liable for postings delivered to this Web site using your account. Any violation of these provisions can subject your account to immediate termination and, possibly, further legal action.
WTVQ and this station do not control and are not responsible for any notes, messages, billboard postings, ideas, suggestions, concepts or other material, or files delivered to this Web site by you or other users. We are not obligated to and do not regularly review, monitor, delete, or edit postings. However, we reserve the right to do so at any time in our sole discretion, for any reason or no reason, and to delete or edit any posting with or without notice. We are not responsible or liable for damages of any kind arising from any postings even when we are advised of the possibility of such damages, or from our alteration or deletion of any posting.
The information and opinions expressed in postings on this Web site are not necessarily those of WTVQ, this station or its content providers, advertisers, sponsors, affiliated or related entities, and we make no representations or warranties regarding that information or those opinions. We do not represent or guarantee the truthfulness, accuracy, or reliability of any postings or determine whether the postings violate the rights of others. You acknowledge that any reliance on material posted by other users will be at your own risk.
Unless otherwise provided, all postings to this Web site automatically become the property of WTVQ and this station without any obligation of confidentiality. We shall be entitled to use the material for any type of use forever including in any media whether now known or later devised. If any court determines that we do not retain exclusive ownership of any posting, then you hereby expressly grant to WTVQ and this station a royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable right to use, reproduce, adapt, modify, publish, edit, translate, perform, transmit, sell, sublicense or otherwise distribute and display the Posting for any reason, including for promotional and advertising purposes, alone or as a part of other works in any form, medium or technology now known or later developed, and you waive all moral rights in all such postings.
Premium Service Additional Terms
You may register for a Premium Service by reading and agreeing to the Terms of Use Agreement and these Premium Service Additional Terms, and by completing the registration form. If you do not agree to abide by the Terms of Use Agreement and these Premium Service Additional Terms, you may not register for the Premium Service.
Member Account and Password
You are responsible for any membership name and password that is associated with your account during registration. If this Premium Service does not recognize your device from a previous sign-in, you will be asked for information that will help us to identify your registration. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your password, if one is established. You are responsible for any and all activities that occur under your account, and agree to notify us immediately of any unauthorized use of your account.
Charges for Premium Service
We will provide notice of any charges, or extra charges, before you register for or enter a premium area. You are responsible for any charges for premium content incurred by your account. We are not liable for any loss that you may incur as a result of someone else using your password or account, whether with or without your knowledge.
In the event that you pay for a Premium Service by credit card, you authorize us to charge your credit card account by registering for the service and providing us with your credit card information. You warrant to us that the credit card information that you provide us is correct and is your account.
Limited to Personal and Non-Commercial Use
This Premium Service is for your personal and non-commercial use only. You may not modify, copy, distribute, transmit, display, perform, reproduce, publish, license, create derivative works from, transfer, or sell any information, software, products obtained from this Premium Service without our prior written consent. You may inquire about obtaining written permission from us to display or reproduce material from this site by writing:
WTVQ
Cancellation
You may cancel your membership in this Premium Service at any time by contacting us using the contact information provided on this Premium Service. In the event that you have paid a fee to register on this site, we will return the unused portion of your membership fee on a 52-week pro-rated basis within ninety (90) days of your cancellation of your membership. We reserve the right to terminate your access to this Premium Service or any portion thereof at any time, without notice. Upon such termination, we shall return the unused pro-rata portion of your membership fee on a 52-week pro-rated basis to you within ninety (90) days of the termination of your access to this service.
Modification of these Terms of Use
We may from time to time change the terms and conditions governing this Premium Service. It is important that you regularly review these terms and conditions to stay informed with regard to any changes in the terms and conditions governing your use of this Premium Service. Your continued use of this Premium Service constitutes your agreement to all such terms and conditions.
Submissions
Unless otherwise stated, we will not review or consider any unsolicited submissions to this Premium Service. All submissions to this Premium Service become our property. No submission will be subject to any reimbursement or other payment by us.
Service Contact
You may email your requests for customer service through the contact information provided on the home page of this Premium Service.
Privacy Statement
This statement informs you of WTVQ?s and this station’s practices with respect to the online collection, use, and disclosure of personal information from this Web site. This Privacy Statement applies to personal information collected through this Web site, but not to WTVQ or this station?s offline business activities.
Personal information is information that allows us to contact you (such as email address, home address, or telephone number) or other information that, when linked to your name or contact information, allows us to personalize your visit to our site by providing you with information that suits your interests. WTVQ and this station are the owners of this website and retain all ownership rights to the information collected at this site. We reserve the right to change, modify, add, or remove provisions of this Privacy Statement. Any changes to this Privacy Statement will be posted here, and we encourage you to review it periodically so that you are up to date on our most current policies and practices.
Personalization
Although you may use many features of this site without completing a registration or sign-up form, visitors who do register and/or sign up for special services may have access to additional features of the site and are more likely to receive information suited to their interests. For example, a registered user is eligible for additional services provided by this website such as listener clubs, interactive services such as chat room or blogs, and personalized content. Our registration and special services sign-up forms may ask you for contact information (like name or email address) and demographic information (like zip code or age). You must provide the information in order to receive the benefits of registration or of the special service.
We may use the contact information you give us to better tailor your Web site experience to your interests, and to send you information about us and our services as well as promotional material on behalf of some of our partners. We use other information that you provide to us to show you content in which you may be interested and to display the content according to your preferences. We will also share this information within the WTVQ family in order to enhance your experience on this and other WTVQ Web sites.
In addition, we may share this information with advertisers or other third parties that are not part of the WTVQ family on an aggregate or other basis that does not disclose your identity or contact information.
Online Surveys/Contests
From time to time, we may conduct online surveys and contests. These ask you for contact information (like name or email address) and demographic information (like zip code or age). We may use this contact information from our surveys and contests to provide you with information about our company and promotional material on behalf of some of our partners, and to contact you when necessary.
Supplemental Information
To enhance our ability to tailor this site to your preferences, we may combine information that you provide us on registration and other online sign-up forms with other information about you that we may obtain. We do not share that information with any other party.
Shopping/Commercial Services
This Web site may offer shopping services, which may be offered by us or by a firm that operates a store under contract with us. If our Web site offers shopping or other commercial services, you will use a customer order form to request information, products, and services. The order form will ask you to give us contact information (like name or email address), financial information (like account or credit card numbers), and demographic information (like zip code or age).
We will use the financial information that you provide to bill you for products and services. By giving us your credit card and related personal information, you are authorizing our store to give that information to the merchant and credit card company in order to confirm and fulfill your order.
We will use contact information from the order form to fulfill your orders. We may also use contact data to get in touch with you when necessary. We will not otherwise use or distribute your financial information without your prior approval.
Public Forums
This site may make available chat rooms, forums, message boards, and news groups. Please remember that any information that you disclose in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.
Information Sharing With Third Parties
From time to time we may enter into a special relationship with another company that is not owned by WTVQ to provide additional features at this site. These special relationships may include “powered by” partners, business partners, sponsors, and co-branded sites (referred to here as “co-branded pages”). These might include, for example, pages that share our name and that of another entity, such as TicketMaster. You should look for a specific privacy statement on any such co-branded page. Any personal information that you provide when signing up at one of those co-branded pages may be shared with our third party partner. You should also check our partner?s website for information regarding its privacy policies.
Also, the nature of some features of our Web site may require that we share personal information about you with persons or companies outside of the WTVQ family. For example, this may occur at a feature that enables you to ask questions of persons or entities that are not part of the WTVQ family. By responding to those features, whether by email or direct entry of information on our Web site, you are consenting to our transferring that information to such persons or entities.
With respect to specific registration modules, like contests, we may disclose personal information collected, and we will post a conspicuous statement on the registration module to the effect that we will be disclosing the information collected with third parties.
Finally, we may share any of the information collected from you with these other non-WTVQ companies in an aggregate basis. The aggregated information is not linked to any information that can identify you.
IP Address and Log Files
We may use your IP address to administer our Web site, to help diagnose problems with our server, to analyze trends, to track users? webpage movements, to help identify you and your shopping cart, and to gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.
Cookies
This Web site may use a standard technology called a “cookie” to collect information about how you use the site. Cookies reside on your computer and help our Web site to recognize your computer’s browser as a previous visitor. This information allows us to customize delivery of information. For example, our Web site may use cookies to save and remember registration information or preferences that you may have set while browsing here previously, to keep track of your shopping cart, to ensure you don’t see the same ad content repeatedly, to deliver content specific to your interests, and to save your password so you don’t have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. We use cookies only to gather information as indicated in this policy. In addition, on occasion our site may also set a “session cookie” which helps us administer the Web site. The session cookie expires when you close your browser and does not retain any information about you after it expires.
Finally, we may also use an ad network provider to help present advertisements on this and other WTVQ Web sites. This ad network provider, like other advertising service vendors, uses cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies on the hard drive of your computer to serve you advertisements tailored to interests you have shown by browsing on this and other sites you have visited, and to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before and to avoid sending you duplicate advertisements. In doing so, the provider collects non-personal data such as your browser type, your operating system, Web pages visited, time of visits, content viewed, ads viewed, and other clickstream data. The use of cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies by these ad network providers is subject to their own privacy policies, not ours. If you do not want the benefits of these advertising cookies, you may opt-out by visiting http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp. However, if you do so you may not receive the full benefit from the use of our site.
Banner Advertising
We license ad-server software from another company to place banner advertising on our Web sites. All of the data provided and generated by the ad-server software remains in our possession and no data is transferred to the licensor of the software. This feature may, on occasion, set “cookies” on your computer. Any information collected or stored by the ad-service or the cookies is treated in the same manner as other information as described in this statement.
Children?s Personal Information
Consistent with the Children?s Online Privacy Protection Act:
? This site does NOT collect, use, or disclose personal information (including online contact information) of children under the age of 13.
? In the event that a child under the age of 13 attempts to register on our site, we will NOT accept the registration and will delete information received from the child.
? In the event that a child posts personal information in a public forum such as a chat room, we will attempt to delete that information once we become aware of it.
Your Choices
This Web site provides you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving email communications from us and our special relationship partners. To opt-out of receiving email communications, you may:
? Modify your registered user information on our Web site; or
? Send an email to Inergize Digital Media. Please include the web address, call letters or station’s name. (Please note that this email address should only be used for specific technical issues related to the website such as unsubscribing from a database. The recipients of these emails will not be able, in general to answer concerns regarding on-air programming, promotions or other non-web related issues.)
Access to Personal Information
We give you the opportunity to modify or remove personal information that you have provided to us. You may do so by modifying your password-protected registered user information on our Web site.
Security of Your Personal Information
We employ security measures, consistent with standard industry practice, for information collected through this website. We believe that we have adequate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of the information we collect on our website. We also use internal protections to limit access to users’ personal information to only those employees who need the information to perform a specific job.
Sale or Merger
If this site is sold to, or merges with, another company not owned by WTVQ, you should expect that some or all of the information collected from this website may be transferred to the buyer/surviving company. If so, we will seek to obligate the acquiring company to use any personal information transferred by this site in a manner consistent with this statement, but cannot guarantee that it will be able to impose that requirement or that the acquiring company will comply.
Legal Process
You should be aware that we may be required to disclose your personal information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, such as in court or regulatory proceedings.
Your Neighbors. Your News.
Talk To UsTalk to ABC 36 News anchors, reporters and meteorologists. When you see news happening, share it! We’d love to hear from you.
859-299-3636|news36@wtvq.com
6940 Man O' War Blvd. Lexington, KY 40509
Watch UsWe live, work and play right here in Central Kentucky. We are your neighbors. We celebrate community and we tell your stories. We are the most trusted source for local news.
Get AlertsDownload the ABC 36 News App on your smart phone or tablet device to receive breaking news and weather push notifications the minute it happens.
Mobile App|Weather App
HOMEContact Us
Advertising
Our News Team
Mobile Apps
FCC
Jobs
RSS Feeds
